export const data = [
    {
      question : "Whitch of the following tag is used to make the underlined text?",
      option1: "<i>",
      option2: "<ul>",
      option3: "<u>",
      option4: "<pre>",
      ans : 3 ,
    },
    {
        question : "Whitch is the correct CSS syntax?",
        option1: "body {color:black}",
        option2: "{body;color:black}",
        option3: "{body:color=black{body}",
        option4: "body:color=black",
        ans : 1 ,
      },
      {
        question : "Whitch of the following keywords is used to define a variable in JavaScript?",
        option1: "var",
        option2: "let",
        option3: "var and let",
        option4: "None of the above",
        ans : 3 ,
      },
     
      {
        question : "Whitch of the following tag is used to define options in a drop-down selection list?",
        option1: "<select>",
        option2: "<list>",
        option3: "<dropdown>",
        option4: "<option>",
        ans : 2 ,
      },
      
      {
        question : "Whitch of the following CSS Property controls how an element is positioned?",
        option1: "static",
        option2: "position",
        option3: "fix",
        option4: "<option>",
        ans : 2 ,
      },
      {
        question : "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type",
        option1: "const",
        option2: "var",
        option3: "let",
        option4: "constant",
        ans : 1 ,
      },
      {
        question : "Whitch character is used to represent the closing of a tag in HTML?",
        option1: " \ ",
        option2: "!",
        option3: "/",
        option4: ".",
        ans : 3 ,
      },
      {
        question : "In CSS ,fontsize can be called as?",
        option1: "Selector",
        option2: "Rule",
        option3: "Property",
        option4: "Property-Name",
        ans : 3,
      },
      {
        question : "Whitch of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using JavaScript?",
        option1: "document.write()",
        option2: "console.log()",
        option3: "window.aiert",
        option4: "All of the above",
        ans : 4 ,
      },
      {
        question : "Whitch of the following HTML tag is used to create an unordered list?",
        option1: "<ol>",
        option2: "<ul>",
        option3: "<li>",
        option4: "<ll>",
        ans : 2 ,
      }

];